# Connor Douglas

cpd8405@stern.nyu.edu | connordouglas10.github.io| linkedin.com/in/cpdouglas/

44 W 4th St., KMC 8-180, New York, NY 10012 | U.S. Citizen

#### Вю

My research interests broadly lie at the intersection of computation and economics. More specifically, I am interested in data-driven decision-making, adaptive learning and experimentation, and personalization.

I am grateful to be supported by the NSF Graduate Research Fellowship Program (GRFP) and NYU Stern doctoral program.

Interests: machine learning, reinforcement learning, data-driven decision-making, personalization, markets, social media, multi-agent systems

#### **EDUCATION**

#### New York University, Stern School of Business

2022 - Present

Ph.D. Information Systems — Technology, Operations, & Statistics department

New York, NY

- Grade: 3.9/4.0
- Advisors: Foster Provost, Arun Sundararajan

# Washington University in St. Louis

2018 - 2022

B.S. Computer Science & Economics — McKelvey School of Engineering

St. Louis, MO

- Grade: 3.98/4.0, Summa Cum Laude
- Minor: Design

#### Professional Experience

United Nations

Nov. 2023 – May 2024

Data Science Research Fellow

New York, NY

Adressing mis/disinformation in peacekeeping

- Studied methods for identifying mis/disinformation relevant to UN peacekeeping
- · Constructed novel method of detecting coordinated behavior through semantic similarity of social media content
- Built social media monitoring tool to track narratives circulating on social media channels
- Designed sampling methods for adaptive learning of sentence embedding models

Genentech

May 2020 - May 2021

Software Engineering Intern

South San Francisco, CA

- Developed novel technique for creating structured data from unstructured clinical trial protocols
- Led project in developing full-stack clinical study management tool
- Designed and built front-end of question-answering tool ingesting protocol documents

### **PUBLICATIONS**

### Naive Algorithmic Collusion: When Do Bandit Learners Cooperate and When Do They Compete?

Connor Douglas, Foster Provost, Arun Sundararajan

Proceedings of ICIS 2024 (forthcoming). 2024.

#### Computing an Optimal Strategy in a Baseball At-bat

Connor Douglas, Everett Witt, Mia Bendy, Yevgeniy Vorobeychik

Proceedings of FLAIRS-36 Conference. 2023.

#### Techniques for Abstraction of Unstructured Clinical Trial Health Data

Lukas Corey\*, Jennifer Crawford\*, Connor Douglas\*, Benjamin Fernandez\*

\*Equal Contributions

U.S. Patent Office Filing (PCT/US22/30369). 2022.

#### RESEARCH-IN-PROGRESS

### Domain Adaptation of Sentence-level Embedding Models with LLM Feedback

Connor Douglas

# Teaching Experience

Microeconomics (Undergraduate) Fall 2024 Teaching Fellow New York University — Stern School of Business Intro. to Analytics and AI (Graduate) Summer 2024 Teaching Fellow New York University — Stern School of Business Data Science for Business (Graduate) Spring 2024 Teaching Fellow New York University — Stern School of Business Intro. to Econometrics (Undergraduate) Spring 2022 Teaching Assistant Washington University in St. Louis — Economics Department Data Structures & Algorithms (Undergraduate) Fall 2019, Spring 2020 Teaching Assistant Washington University in St. Louis — Computer Science Department

Institutional Service **ISPOC** 2024 Associate Organizer Tau Beta Pi (WUSTL Chapter) 2021-2022 PresidentEngineers Without Borders (WUSTL Chapter) 2019-2021 Treasurer

#### Presentations and Invited Talks

Topics in Data Science: Guest lecture on multi-armed bandits and reinforcement learning. 2024.

**FLAIRS-36 Conference**: Oral presentation on Computing an Optimal Strategy in a Baseball At-bat. 2023.

# Grants and Awards

NSF GRFP: Award won in Economics (2024); Total Funding: \$159,000

National Merit Scholarship: Scholarship awarded by Pfizer (2018); Total Funding: \$12,000

#### Selected Graduate Coursework

- Advanced Topics in Data Driven Decision Making
- No-regret Learning in Games
- Machine Learning and Sequential Decision Making
- Stochastic Processes
- Topics in Data Science
- Topics in Digital Economics
- Technical Foundations of Information Systems
- Real Analysis
- Convex Optimization
- Reinforcement Learning
- Human-in-the-loop Computation